http://www.literock969.com/vip-terms/

What's Hot:Christmas 202012 DaysLight Up South JerseyToys for TotsVirtual Job FairCOVID-19: The LatestImpossible TriviaHealth UpdateSouth Jersey DealsPet of the WeekNJ Business ExchangeFlashback CafeSign InHomeOn-AirAll DJsScheduleEddie DavisNicole MurrayGary GuidaDelilahRobin StoloffListenListen LiveMobile AppAlexaGoogle HomeRecently PlayedAppDownload iOSDownload AndroidWin StuffLight Up South Jersey$100 Wawa Gift CardSign UpContest RulesContest SupportEventsCalendarSubmit Your EventContact UsHelp & Contact InfoSend FeedbackAdvertiseMoreHomeOn-AirAll DJsScheduleEddie DavisNicole MurrayGary GuidaDelilahRobin StoloffListenListen LiveMobile AppAlexaGoogle HomeRecently PlayedAppDownload iOSDownload AndroidWin StuffLight Up South Jersey$100 Wawa Gift CardSign UpContest RulesContest SupportEventsCalendarSubmit Your EventContact UsHelp & Contact InfoSend FeedbackAdvertiseListen NowLite Rock 96.9Lite Rock 96.9INSTAGRAMVIP TermsTerms and conditionsThe Lite Rock Listener Club (the "Service"), operated by Townsquare Media, Inc., and (LITE ROCK 96.9) ("we," or "us") is provided to you ("you," "your" or "User") under the following terms and conditions, including any amendments thereto and any additional terms and conditions, rules or policies that may be applicable to particular offerings made in connection with the Service (collectively, the "Terms and Conditions"). We reserve the right to update or change these Terms and Conditions from time to time. Any such changes shall be reflected in an updated version of the Terms and Conditions posted on this site. By continuing to use the Service following the posting of any such change, you will be deemed to have agreed to the amended version of the Terms and Conditions. Any failure to comply with these Terms and Conditions by you may result in the termination of your account, and the forfeiture and relinquishment of all Entries you have accrued in the Service. BY REGISTERING TO USE THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, SO PLEASE READ THEM CAREFULLY.Description of the ServiceThe Service is a program where registered users can enter Contests or Sweepstakes by engaging in certain activities and can redeem prizes, benefits, or opportunities ("Rewards"). Some Rewards provided through the Service by way of sweepstakes or trade-ins are promoted regionally or nationally to users of other rewards services. Rewards that are promoted and accessible only to users eligible to participate in this Service are noted as such by the display of the reward type 'L' on the page displaying the material terms for that sweepstake, or trade-in. Rewards promoted and accessible in multiple markets to users of this Service and other rewards services are noted as such by display of the reward type 'MM' on the page displaying the material terms for that sweepstake, auction or trade-in.EligibilityUnless otherwise specified in connection with particular offerings, participation in the Service is open only to natural persons who are local residents and who are 18 years of age or older. You must have a valid street address in the United States. (a P.O. Box address will not suffice). Employees or agents of LITE ROCK 96.9, Townsquare Media, Inc., and each of their respective affiliates, subsidiaries, and parent companies and immediate family members of or persons domiciled with any such persons are not eligible to participate.Reservation of RightsThe Service and its benefits are offered at our discretion, and we have the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service, in whole or in part for any reason, at our sole discretion. We may, among other things, withdraw, limit, modify or cancel any Reward; increase the Entries required for any Reward; or modify or condition the transferability of Rewards or benefits. You agree that we will not be liable to you or any third-party for any modification or discontinuance of the Service, in whole or in part.Membership registrationIn consideration of your use of the Service, you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the registration form and to maintain and promptly update your personal data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or if we or any of our service providers have reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, we have the right to suspend or terminate your account and to refuse any and all current or future use of the Service (or any portion thereof) by you. You may not register with a disposable email address. Only one member account per person and two member accounts per household are permitted. If you are less than 18 years of age you cannot post information about yourself on the website or complete the registration process. You can, among other things, review your accumulated Entries, review the Terms and Conditions as amended from time to time, and review redemption options at in the footer of the LITE ROCK 96.9 website.Account securityYou will create a password and account designation upon completing the registration process. You agree to maintain the confidentiality of your password and account, and that you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and to exit from your account at the end of each session. We will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with these conditions.Privacy PolicyBy participating in the Service, you agree that we may collect and use information about you that you provide to us in accordance with our Privacy Policy. For more information, see our Privacy Policy to see our complete privacy policy. By using the Service, you agree to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Policy.Limitation of Liability, Indemnity and ReleaseUNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL WE BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES (EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), ARISING FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE OR ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, IN SUCH STATES, OUR LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. BY USING THE SERVICE YOU AGREE THAT OUR TOTAL LIABILITY FOR ANY ACTION, CLAIM OR JUDGMENT, REGARDLESS OF THE NATURE OF THE CLAIM OR THEORY OF LIABILITY, SHALL BE LIMITED TO YOUR ACTUAL OUT OF POCKET EXPENSES INCURRED IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE, BUT IN NO EVENT ATTORNEY'S FEES. You accept all responsibility for, and hereby indemnify and hold us harmless from and against, any actions taken by any user authorized to use your account, including, but not limited to, accrual of Entries, redemption of Entries, and disclosure of passwords to third parties. By using the Service, you release us, our subsidiaries, and affiliates from any and all liability regarding the redemption of Entries, use of Rewards, or other participation in the Service.Violation of the TermsYou understand and agree that in our sole discretion, and without prior notice, we may remove Entries from your account as a penalty, terminate your access to the website or deactivate your membership account if we determine that you have violated our Terms and Conditions.IndemnityYou agree to indemnify and hold us, our subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents and other partners and employees, harmless from any loss, liability, claim or demand, including reasonable attorney's fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your use of the website, including, without limitation, any information or content you post to the site or any interference with the operation of the site.MiscellaneousThese Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state, without giving effect to any conflicts or choice of laws rules (whether this state or any other jurisdiction). The invalidity or unenforceability of any provisions of these Terms and Conditions shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision. In the event that any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found to be invalid or unenforceable, these Terms and Conditions shall be construed in accordance with their terms as if the invalid or unenforceable provision was not contained therein. The Service and its components, including all trademarks, trade names and logos, are the property of Townsquare Media, Inc. and/or its licensors, which reserves all rights to such property.Eddie DavisRead ArticlesNicole MurrayRead ArticlesGary GuidaRead ArticlesRobin StoloffRead ArticlesDelilahRead ArticlesJohn TeshRead Articles Sign up to get exclusive access to VIP events, contests, coupons, giveaways, presales and much more!Sign Up NowNJ looks to ban packing peanuts as part of plastic recycling bill25 minutes agoStores That Are Open Late and 24 Hours for Last Minute Christmas 7 hours agoEgg Harbor City Invites You to Join Its Christmas Car Parade7 hours agoEllen DeGeneres Tests Positive for COVID-198 hours agoDevote more time to running your business.Engage your clients across multiple platforms.Reach more customers than ever before.Get an Edge on the Competition Today!
